{"deck":  { "title": "US Capitol Cities", "categories": ["History", "Geography"], "cards": [
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Louisiana?", "answer": "Baton Rouge\nDate of statehood: 1812\nCapitol since: 1880\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Delaware?", "answer": "Dover\nDate of statehood: 1787\nCapitol since: 1777\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of California?", "answer": "Sacramento\nDate of statehood: 1850\nCapitol since: 1854\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of North Carolina?", "answer": "Raleigh\nDate of statehood: 1789\nCapitol since: 1794\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of New Jersey?", "answer": "Trenton\nDate of statehood: 1787\nCapitol since: 1784\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Illinois?", "answer": "Springfield\nDate of statehood: 1818\nCapitol since: 1837\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Nebraska?", "answer": "Lincoln\nDate of statehood: 1867\nCapitol since: 1867\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Kentucky?", "answer": "Frankfort\nDate of statehood: 1792\nCapitol since: 1792\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Iowa?", "answer": "Des Moines\nDate of statehood: 1846\nCapitol since: 1857\nMost populous city? Yes"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Minnesota?", "answer": "Saint Paul\nDate of statehood: 1858\nCapitol since: 1849\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Oregon?", "answer": "Salem\nDate of statehood: 1859\nCapitol since: 1855\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of South Dakota?", "answer": "Pierre\nDate of statehood: 1889\nCapitol since: 1889\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Washington?", "answer": "Olympia\nDate of statehood: 1889\nCapitol since: 1853\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Georgia?", "answer": "Atlanta\nDate of statehood: 1788\nCapitol since: 1868\nMost populous city? Yes"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Vermont?", "answer": "Montpelier\nDate of statehood: 1791\nCapitol since: 1805\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Oklahoma?", "answer": "Oklahoma City\nDate of statehood: 1907\nCapitol since: 1910\nMost populous city? Yes"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Alabama?", "answer": "Montgomery\nDate of statehood: 1819\nCapitol since: 1846\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of New York?", "answer": "Albany\nDate of statehood: 1788\nCapitol since: 1797\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of New Hampshire?", "answer": "Concord\nDate of statehood: 1788\nCapitol since: 1808\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Idaho?", "answer": "Boise\nDate of statehood: 1890\nCapitol since: 1865\nMost populous city? Yes"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Kansas?", "answer": "Topeka\nDate of statehood: 1861\nCapitol since: 1856\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Montana?", "answer": "Helena\nDate of statehood: 1889\nCapitol since: 1875\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Indiana?", "answer": "Indianapolis\nDate of statehood: 1816\nCapitol since: 1825\nMost populous city? Yes"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Rhode Island?", "answer": "Providence\nDate of statehood: 1790\nCapitol since: 1900\nMost populous city? Yes"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of South Carolina?", "answer": "Columbia\nDate of statehood: 1788\nCapitol since: 1786\nMost populous city? Yes"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Missouri?", "answer": "Jefferson City\nDate of statehood: 1821\nCapitol since: 1826\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Arkansas?", "answer": "Little Rock\nDate of statehood: 1836\nCapitol since: 1821\nMost populous city? Yes"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Virginia?", "answer": "Richmond\nDate of statehood: 1788\nCapitol since: 1780\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Wisconsin?", "answer": "Madison\nDate of statehood: 1848\nCapitol since: 1838\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Utah?", "answer": "Salt Lake City\nDate of statehood: 1896\nCapitol since: 1858\nMost populous city? Yes"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Massachusetts?", "answer": "Boston\nDate of statehood: 1788\nCapitol since: 1630\nMost populous city? Yes"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Ohio?", "answer": "Columbus\nDate of statehood: 1803\nCapitol since: 1816\nMost populous city? Yes"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Michigan?", "answer": "Lansing\nDate of statehood: 1837\nCapitol since: 1847\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Maine?", "answer": "Augusta\nDate of statehood: 1820\nCapitol since: 1832\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Florida?", "answer": "Tallahassee\nDate of statehood: 1845\nCapitol since: 1824\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Colorado?", "answer": "Denver\nDate of statehood: 1876\nCapitol since: 1867\nMost populous city? Yes"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of North Dakota?", "answer": "Bismarck\nDate of statehood: 1889\nCapitol since: 1883\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of New Mexico?", "answer": "Santa Fe\nDate of statehood: 1912\nCapitol since: 1610\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Tennessee?", "answer": "Nashville\nDate of statehood: 1796\nCapitol since: 1826\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Nevada?", "answer": "Carson City\nDate of statehood: 1864\nCapitol since: 1861\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Pennsylvania?", "answer": "Harrisburg\nDate of statehood: 1787\nCapitol since: 1812\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of West Virginia?", "answer": "Charleston\nDate of statehood: 1863\nCapitol since: 1885\nMost populous city? Yes"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Mississippi?", "answer": "Jackson\nDate of statehood: 1817\nCapitol since: 1821\nMost populous city? Yes"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Arizona?", "answer": "Phoenix\nDate of statehood: 1912\nCapitol since: 1889\nMost populous city? Yes"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Wyoming?", "answer": "Cheyenne\nDate of statehood: 1890\nCapitol since: 1869\nMost populous city? Yes"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Hawaii?", "answer": "Honolulu\nDate of statehood: 1959\nCapitol since: 1845\nMost populous city? Yes"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Connecticut?", "answer": "Hartford\nDate of statehood: 1788\nCapitol since: 1875\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Alaska?", "answer": "Juneau\nDate of statehood: 1959\nCapitol since: 1906\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Texas?", "answer": "Austin\nDate of statehood: 1845\nCapitol since: 1839\nMost populous city? No"}},
{"card": {"question": "What is the Capitol of Maryland?", "answer": "Annapolis\nDate of statehood: 1788\nCapitol since: 1694\nMost populous city? No"}}]}
}
